A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A93), 1985-1993; 1.19; 121.03 Cubic Feet; 274 letter size document boxes and 1 legal size document box; Boxes 1-275
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 87048 A22 - International Potato Center (CIP) - "Farmers and Food Systems" Workshop, 1988-1991, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 422, Box 69, Folder 423)
      Centro Internacional de la Papa (CIP)
    - RF 87051 - Management Sciences for Health, 1986-1990 (Box 69, Folder 424-425)
    - RF 87052 - University of Newcastle, Australia - Asian and Pacific Centre for Clinical Epidemiology, 1978-1991 (Box 69, Folder 426-428, Box 70, Folder 429-432)
      Formerly 197
      Centre for Clinical Epidemiology and Biostatistics formerly known as Asian and Pacific Centre for Clinical Epidemiology
    - RF 87052 - University of Newcastle, Australia - Asian and Pacific Centre for Clinical Epidemiology: Supplementary Material (Box 70, Folder 433)
    - RF 87054 - New York International Festival of the Arts, Inc. - Third World and American Minority Artists, 1986-1989 (Box 70, Folder 434, Box 71, Folder 435-439)
    - RF 87056 A238 - Omideyi, Adekunbi 'Kehinde, 1984-1988, 1990, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 440-441)
      Research on women's status and fertility among the Yoruba in Nigeria
    - RF 87056 A239 - Tashakkori, Abbas, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 442-443)
      Project proposal: Study of how the Islamic Revolution has changed Iranian adolescents' attitudes regarding marriage, fertility and the status of women
    - RF 87056 A243 - Gates, Hill, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 444)
      Study of fertility and women's capital in Taiwan
    - RF 87056 A244 - Mahmud, Simeen, 1987-1992, 1994, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 445, Box 73, Folder 446-447)
      Study of how the status and fertility of Bangladeshi women is affected by their participation in income-earning projects
    - RF 87056 A247 - Institute for Resource Development, Inc. - Women's Employment Survey, 1986-1990 (Box 73, Folder 448-450)
    - RF 87056 A250 - Sather, Zeba Ayesha, 1984-1990, 1992, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 451-453)
      Research to measure changes in women's status and fertility in Karachi, Pakistan
      Formerly 150(465)
    - RF 87056 A253 - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Workshops on Women's Status and Fertility, 1984-1989, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 454-455, Box 75, Folder 456-461, Box 76, Folder 462-465)
    - RF 87056 A253 - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Workshops on Women's Status and Fertility: Supplementary Material (Box 76, Folder 466-467, Box 77, Folder 468)
    - RF 87058 A66 - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) - Development of Anther Culture in Rice Breeding Program, 1985-1991 (Box 77, Folder 469-472, Box 78, Folder 473)
      International Center of Tropical Agriculture
    - RF 87058 A69 - Texas A & M University - Genotypic Variation in Rooting Parameters, 1988-1990 (Box 78, Folder 474)
    - RF 87058 A70 - University of Georgia - Rice Genes, 1984-1991 (Box 78, Folder 475-476)
      Formerly 200D
    - RF 87058 A71- International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Rice Genetics Research, 1985-1990 (Box 78, Folder 477-479, Box 79, Folder 480)
    - RF 87058 A72 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Equipment and Research in Rice Pathology, 1985-1990, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 481-482)
    - RF 87058 A73 - Philippine Rice Research Institute - Collaboration with Japan and Thailand, 1988-1991, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 483-484)
    - RF 87058 A76 - Plant Genetic Systems, Belgium - Insect Pests of Rice, 1988, 1990-1992, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 485)
      Research on the use of Bacillus thuringiensis toxin genes to control insect pests of rice
    - RF 87058 A78 - University of Wisconsin, Madison - Rice Disease, 1985-1990, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 486-487)
      Research on the genome organization of Pyricularia oryzae, the causative organism of blast disease in rice
    - RF 87063 - Arts and Business Council, Inc., 1979-1991 (Box 80, Folder 488-490, Box 81, Folder 491-495, Box 82, Folder 496-501, Box 83, Folder 502-506, Box 84, Folder 507-509)
    - RF 87063 - Arts and Business Council, Inc.: Supplementary Material (Box 84, Folder 510-511, Box 85, Folder 512-516, Box 86, Folder 517-521, Box 87, Folder 522-526, Box 88, Folder 527)
    - RF 87064 A1 - Center Theatre Group of Los Angeles - Munich and Vienna Performances, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 528)
    - RF 87064 A2 - Orpheus Chamber Orchestra, New York - Bath International Festival of Music and Arts, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 529)
    - RF 87064 A3 - (The) Biennale of Sydney - American Entries in 1988 Biennale (Box 88, Folder 530)
    - RF 87064 A5 - (The) Boston Camerata - Singapore Festival for the Arts, 1988-1990 (Box 88, Folder 531)
    - RF 87064 A6 - Taylor, Billy, 1988-1990 (Box 88, Folder 532)
      Participation of the Billy Taylor Trio at the Third International Music Festival - Music for Humanism, Peace, and Friends Among Nations in Leningrad, U.S.S.R.
    - RF 87064 A7 - Stephen Petronio Dance Company, Inc., New York - The Holland Festival and Festival International Montpellier-Danse, 1988-1989 (Box 88, Folder 533)
    - RF 87064 A8 - Music-Theatre Performing Group, Inc., New York - Festival de Otono, Madrid, and Festival de Ville, Paris, 1988-1989 (Box 88, Folder 534)
    - RF 87064 A9 - Original Ballets Foundation, New York - Italian Festivals, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 535)
      Festivals: Estate Palermitana; Pistoia Piazza del Duomo; Festivale Estivo; Festive Nervi; L'Orta Bottanico della Citta di Roma
    - RF 87064 A10 - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, Inc., New York - 1988 Edinburgh Festival Fringe, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 536)
    - RF 87064 A11 - Zaccho Dance Theatre, San Francisco - Festival d'Arles, France, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 537)
      Zaccho, S.F.
    - RF 87064 A12 - International Congress on Women in Music, California - 1988 International Congress of Women in Music, Germany, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 538)
    - RF 87064 A13 - Philadelphia Museum of Art - 43rd Venice Biennale, 1988-1990 (Box 89, Folder 539)
      Exhibition: "Jasper Johns: Work since 1974"
    - RF 87064 A14 - Trisha Brown Dance Company, Inc., New York - 1988 National Theatre Dance Festival, Taiwan, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 540)
    - RF 87064 A15 - E. Monte Motion, Inc., New York - Solo Mini Arts Festival, Java, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 541)
      Elisa Monte Dance Company
    - RF 87064 A16 - Dance Futures Foundation, New York - Toga Festival, Japan, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 542)
      Presentation of "Invisible Languages"
    - RF 87064 A17 - Syracuse University - Second Biannual International Video Festival, Colombia, 1987-1989 (Box 89, Folder 543)
    - RF 87064 A18 - Moore, Carman L., 1988-1990 (Box 89, Folder 544)
      Participation of the Carman L. Moore Skymusic Ensemble at the "Made in America Festival" in Geneva, Switzerland
    - RF 87064 A19 - Milwaukee Repertory Theater - Toga Festival, Japan, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 545)
      Presentation of "The Tale of Lear" at Toga International Arts Festival, August 1988
    - RF 87064 A20 - Davis, Anthony, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 546)
      Performance of Anthony Davis and Episteme at "Made in America Festival", Geneva, Switzerland
    - RF 87064 A21 - Warshaw, Randy I, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 547)
      Participation of Randy Warshaw Dance Company at London Dance Umbrella's Tenth Annual Festival, October/November 1988
    - RF 87064 A22 - Budapest New York Theatre Arts Foundation, Inc. - Milano Oltre Festival, Italy, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 548)
    - RF 87064 A23 - (The) Dance Exchange, Inc., Washington, D.C. - Dance Umbrella's Tenth Anniversary Festival, London, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 549)
    - RF 87064 A24 - Players' Project, Ltd., New York - Cervantino Festival, Mexico City and Guanajuato, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 550)
    - RF 87064 A25 - Rod Rodgers Dance Company, Inc., New York - First International Festival of Contemporary Dance, Mexico City, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 551)
    - RF 87064 A26 - José Limón Dance Foundation, Inc., New York - Festival Internacional Cervantino and Festival Cultural Sinaloa, Mexico, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 552)
    - RF 87064 A27 - California Institute of the Arts - "Hungers" Performance at Ars Electronica, Linz, Austria, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 553)
    - RF 87064 A28 - Urban Bush Women, New York - Festival International Montpellier-Danse and Dance Umbrella's Tenth Annual Festival, London, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 554)
    - RF 87064 A29 - Mary Luft and Company, Inc., Miami - 1998: Ano Internacional de la Musica Argentina, Buenos Aires, and New York Dagen, Rotterdam, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 555)
    - RF 87064 A30 - Dean Dance and Music Foundation, Inc., New York - Festival de Otono de Madrid, 1988-1990 (Box 90, Folder 556)
    - RF 87065 - Voting Rights, 1981, 1983, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 557-560)
    - RF 87065 A1 - National Coalition on Black Voter Participation, Inc. - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities, 1982-1989, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 561, Box 92, Folder 562-565)
    - RF 87065 A2 - Midwest Voter Registration Education Project - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 566, Box 93, Folder 567-570)
    - RF 87065 A4 - Center for Community Change - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities, 1986-1990 (Box 93, Folder 571-572, Box 94, Folder 573)
    - RF 87065 A5 - Southwest Voter Registration Education Project - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities, 1984-1990 (Box 94, Folder 574-575)
    - RF 87065 A6 - American Citizenship Education Project - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities, 1987-1990 (Box 94, Folder 576-577)
    - RF 87065 A6 - American Citizenship Education Project - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities (Box T5)
      VHS Videotape: The Advertising Council VOTE '88: "You Dreamed" Closed Captions; "Political Machine" Closed Captions; "Can't Vote" Closed Captions; "You Dreamed"; "Political Machines"; Can't Vote - Chile"; "Can't Vote - South Africa"
    - RF 87065 A6 - American Citizenship Education Project - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities (Box T5)
      VHS Videotape: Center for Community Change, "1988 Voter Registration Campaign", 19:00, 10/21/88
    - RF 87065 A6 - American Citizenship Education Project - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities (Box T5)
      VHS Videotape: AD Council/ACEP, "1988 Voter Registration Campaign", 29 PSA's, 19:00, A8-09-452, 9/16/88
    - RF 87065 A7 - Voter Education Project, Inc. - Voter Registration Education and Monitoring Activities, 1987-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 94, Folder 578, Box 95, Folder 579-582)
    - RF 87066 - Vaccine Development Capacity in the Third World, 1988-1989 (Box 95, Folder 583)
    - RF 87066 A1 - National Museums of Kenya - Vaccine Development, 1987-1992 (Box 95, Folder 584)
    - RF 87066 A2 - Fundaҫão Oswaldo Cruz, Rio de Janeiro - Vaccine Development, 1985-1992, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 585, Box 96, Folder 586-587)
    - RF 87068 - Program for the Introduction and Adaptation of Contraceptive Technology (PIACT), Seattle - NORPLANT Implants in Developing Countries, 1987-1991 (Box 96, Folder 588)
    - RF 87069 A30 - Chamwali, Anthony A., 1986-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 96, Folder 590-591, Box 97, Folder 592)
      Project title: "Women's Status and Fertility in Zanzibar"
    - RF 87069 A31 - University of Zimbabwe - Male Attitudes and Behavior Concerning Fertility and Contraception, 1987-1990. 1992 (Box 97, Folder 593)
    - RF 87069 A32 - University of Zimbabwe - Dissemination of Information on Population Issues, 1987-1992 (Box 97, Folder 594)
    - RF 87069 A33 - Magembe, Cecil R. M. and Mbago, Maurice C. Y., 1987-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 97, Folder 595-596)
      Research topic: Male perception of spouses' usage of contraception in rural and urban Tanzania
    - RF 87069 A35 - Soyibo, Adedoyin; Oyejide, T. Ademola; Iyun, B. Folasade, 1987-1993 (Box 97, Folder 597, Box 98, Folder 598)
      Research topic: "Impact of Agricultural Development Projects on the Status of Rural Women in Nigeria"
    - RF 87069 A35 - Soyibo, Adedoyin; Oyejide, T. Ademola; Iyun, B. Folasade: Supplementary Material (Box 98, Folder 599-601)
    - RF 87069 A36 - Nyirenda, Vukani G.; Moyo, Steven P. C.; Mufwaya, M. Moola S., 1987-1990, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 602)
      Research topic: "Zambian Perceptions of Supplying Family Planning Services to Adolescents and Unmarried Persons"
    - RF 87069 A41 - University of Nairobi - African Regional Training in Reproductive Health, 1987-1990, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 603)
    - RF 87069 A44 - African Council on Communication Education, Nairobi - Reproductive Health Workshop, 1987-1990 (Box 99, Folder 604-606)
    - RF 87069 A44 - African Council on Communication Education, Nairobi - Reproductive Health Workshop: Supplementary Material (Box 100, Folder 607-609)
    - RF 87069 A45 - University of Dar es Salaam, Tanzania - Reproductive Epidemiology Training, 1988-1991 (Box 100, Folder 610-611)
    - RF 87069 A46 - Udjo, Eric O., 1988-1993 (Box 100, Folder 612, Box 101, Folder 613)
      Research topic: "Patterns of Some Determinants of Fertility in a Northern Nigerian Community"
    - RF 87069 A47 - Sahel Institute, Mali - Drought and Population Dynamics, 1988-1991, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 614)
    - RF 87069 A48 - Kidane, Asmerom, 1988-1992 (Box 101, Folder 615-616)
      Report title: "The Economic Demography of Ethiopia"
    - RF 87069 A51 - University of Kinshasha, Zaire - Population Policy Symposium, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 617)
    - RF 87069 A52 - University of Dar es Salaam, Tanzania - African Population Scholars Conference, 1988-1993 (Box 101, Folder 618)
    - RF 87071 - Overseas Development Council - Minutes (Box 102, Folder 619-620)
    - RF 87071 - Overseas Development Council, 1986-1992 (Box 102, Folder 621-623, Box 103, Folder 624-625)
    - RF 87071 - Overseas Development Council: Supplementary Material (Box 103, Folder 626)
    - RF 87072 - European Cooperation Fund, Belgium - Central European Writing Program, 1983-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 627, Box 104, Folder 628- 632)
    - RF 88001 A2- North Carolina State University - African Soil Management Workshop and Training at Yurimaguas, 1987-1989 (Box 104, Folder 633)
    - RF 88003 A17 - Research Center for Rural Development, Beijing - Lin, Justin Yifu, 1987-1990, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 634)
      Study title: "Differential Impact of Modern Rice Technology in Favorable and Unfavorable Production Environment and Limited Rural Factor Markets in China"
    - RF 88003 A20 - Stanford University - Plant Biotechnology, 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 635)
    - RF 88003 A23 - Chen, Dabai, 1987-1990 (Box 105, Folder 636)
    - RF 88003 A23 - Chen, Dabai, 1987-1990 (Box 105, Folder 636A)
    - RF 88003 A24 - Rozelle, Scott, 1988-1990 (Box 105, Folder 637)
    - RF 88003 A25 - Gadjah Mada University, Indonesia - Rice Farming in Lampung, Indonesia, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 105, Folder 638)
    - RF 88003 A26 - University of Minnesota - Regional Productivity Growth in China's Agriculture, 1987-1991 (Box 105, Folder 639)
    - RF 88003 A27 - Development Research and Management Services (DRMS), Pakistan - Wheat Production in Pakistan, 1989-1993 (Box 105, Folder 640, Box 106, Folder 641)
    - RF 88004 - World Bank - Compact Agricultural Research Library, 1987-1992 (Box 106, Folder 642-646)
    - RF 88006 - United Nations Food and Agricultural Organization - Regional Workshop on Pesticide Regulatory Principles and Procedures for Latin America and the Caribbean, 1987-1993 (Box 107, Folder 647-649)
    - RF 88007 A129 - University of Nairobi - Clinical Epidemiology Unit, 1988, 1991-1992 (Box 107, Folder 650)
    - RF 88007 A130 - Shanghai Medical University, Jinshan Hospital - Wang Wei Qun, 1987-1988, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 651)
    - RF 88007 A132 - Khon Kaen University, Thailand - Chirawatkul, Aroon, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 652)
    - RF 88007 A133 - University of the Philippines - Beltran, Alfredo, 1988, 1990, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 653)
    - RF 88007 A136 - Escola Paulista de Medicina, Brazil - Streptoccocu pneumoniae and Brazilian Children, 1988, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 654)
      Paulista Medical School
    - RF 88007 A142 - Johns Hopkins University - Multicenter Evaluation of Early Clinical Signs of Pneumania, 1988-1990 (Box 107, Folder 655)
    - RF 88007 A144 - Hospital General de Mexico - Clinical Epidemiology Training, 1988, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 656)
    - RF 88007 A146 - Escola Paulista de Medicina, Brazil - Clinical Epidemiology - Miranda, Claudio, 1988-1990 (Box 107, Folder 657)
    - RF 88007 A151 - Pontificia Universidad Javeriana, Colombia - Clinical Epidemiology - Lozano, Juan Manuel, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 658)
    - RF 88007 A152 - Escola Paulista de Medicina, Brazil - Clinical Epidemiology - Ferraz, Marcos Bosi, 1988, 1990, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 659)
    - RF 88007 A153 - University of Nairobi - Clinical Epidemiology - Onyango, Francis E., 1988-1994 (Box 108, Folder 660)
    - RF 88007 A154 - University of Nairobi - Clinical Epidemiology - Sanghvi, H. C. G., 1988-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 661)
    - RF 88007 A158 - Pontificia Universidad Javeriana, Colombia - Clinical Epidemiology - Rodriguez, Nelcy, 1988-1990 (Box 108, Folder 662)
    - RF 88007 A161 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) - Seventh Annual Meeting, 1987-1991 (Box 108, Folder 663-667, Box 109, Folder 668-672, Box 110, Folder 673)
    - RF 88007 A161 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) - Seventh Annual Meeting: Supplementary Material (Box 110, Folder 674-675)
    - RF 88007 A164 - University of Pennsylvania - Pharmacoepidemiology Curriculum for Use by Clinical Epidemiology Resource and Training Centers (CERTs), 1989, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 676)
    - RF 88007 A165 - University of the Philippines - Clinical Epidemiology - Tan-Torres, Tessa L., 1988-1990 (Box 110, Folder 677)
    - RF 88007 A167 - Chulalongkorn University, Thailand - Aspirin in Preventing the Complications of Rheumatic Heart Disease, 1984-1990, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 678)
    - RF 88007 A168 - McMaster University, Canada - Health Economics Training, 1983-1990 (Box 110, Folder 679)
    - RF 88007 A169 - Shanghai Medical University, Hua Shen Hospital - Clinical Epidemiology - Chen, Xinhua, 1989, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 680)
    - RF 88007 A174 - McMaster University, Canada - Social Sciences Training in the International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) Program, 1987-1990 (Box 111, Folder 681)
    - RF 88007 A174 - McMaster University, Canada - Social Sciences Training in the International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN) Program, 1987-1990 (Box 111, Folder 681A)
    - RF 88007 A176 - University of Nairobi - Clinical Epidemiology Workshop, 1989, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 682)
    - RF 88009 A21 - University of Nairobi - Acceptability of Gossypol-Lubricated Condoms Among Prostitutes in Nairobi, 1987-1989 (Box 111, Folder 683)
    - RF 88009 A24 - Chulalongkorn University, Thailand - Acceptability of Gossypol-Lubricated Condoms Among Prostitutes in Bangkok, 1988, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 684)
    - RF 88009 A27 - University of Zambia - Study to Develop Vaginal Contraceptive Pill, 1987-1988, 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 685)
    - RF 88009 A28 - University of Zambia - Contraceptive Counseling for Young Women at Risk of Repeated Abortion, 1988-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 686)
    - RF 88009 A40 - National Museums of Kenya - Study a Contraceptive Vaccine in Baboons, 1987-1992 (Box 111, Folder 687)
    - RF 88012 A26 - Seattle School District No. 1, Washington - Multicultural Curriculum Project, 1984-1990 (Box 111, Folder 688-689, Box 112, Folder 690-694)
    - RF 88012 A26 - Seattle School District No. 1, Washington - Multicultural Curriculum Project: Supplementary Material (Box 112, Folder 695, Box 113, Folder 696-697)
    - RF 88012 A37 - Los Angeles Unified School District, California - Development of HUMANITAS Academy, 1989-1991 (Box 113, Folder 698-699)
    - RF 88013 A428 - Institute for Advanced Study, New Jersey - Conference on "The Impact of Women's Studies Research on Academic Discourse", 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 700, Box 114, Folder 701)
    - RF 88015 A22 - Gordon, Richard and Hinton, Carmelita, 1988-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 114, Folder 702)
      Film project: "Spiritual Pollution", retitled "The Gate of Heavenly Peace"
    - RF 88017 - lnternational Centre of Theatre Research, France - English-Language Version of "Mahabharata" Film, 1987-1991 (Box 114, Folder 703-705)
    - RF 88027 - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, New York - Third World Artists, 1987-1990 (Box 114, Folder 706)
    - RF 88029 A30 - Real Art Ways, Inc., Connecticut - Interdisciplinary Artists Program, 1985-1990 (Box 115, Folder 707-708)
    - RF 88029 A39 - Nexus Contemporary Art Center, Georgia - Interdisciplinary Artists Program, 1986-1990 (Box 115, Folder 709-710)
    - RF 88030 - St. Louis Art Museum, Missouri - Caribbean Festival Tradition Exhibition, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 711, Box 116, Folder 712-713)
    - RF 88034 - Urban Strategies Council, California, and University of Texas, Austin - University/Community Research, 1988, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 714)
    - RF 88034 A1 - Urban Strategies Council, California - University/Community Research, 1988-1991 (Box 116, Folder 715)
    - RF 88034 A2 - University of Texas, Austin - University/Community Research, 1988-1990 (Box 116, Folder 716)
    - RF 88036 A1 - (The) Ounce of Prevention Fund, Illinois - Adolescent Pregnancy and Parenting, 1987-1991, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 717)
    - RF 88036 A2 - FAMILIAS: The National Council for the Enhancement of Hispanic Children and Families, Texas - Planning Conference, 1987-1990 (Box 116, Folder 718)
    - RF 88036 A4 - Pacific Oaks, California - National MATCH Resource Center for Children of Incarcerated Parents, 1988-1990 (Box 117, Folder 719-721)
    - RF 88036 A5 - University of Pennsylvania - Unmarried Fathers, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 722)
    - RF 88036 A6 - New Haven Public Schools, Connecticut - Consortium of Urban Education, 1986-1989, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 723-724)
    - RF 88038 A33 - Kisseadoo, Samuel, 1987-1988, 1990, 1992-1994 (Box 118, Folder 725)
      African Dissertation Internship Award. Dissertation topic: "The Taxonomy and Ecology of the Trees of the Bobiri Forest Reserve, Ghana, West Africa"
    - RF 88038 A33 - Kisseadoo, Samuel, 1987-1988, 1990, 1992-1994 (Box 118, Folder 725A)
    - RF 88038 A35 - Eshiwani, Arthur A., 1988-1990 (Box 118, Folder 726)
      African Dissertation Internship Award. Dissertation topic: "Taxation of Land in Kenya: A Strategy for Strengthening Local Government Participation in Rural Development"
    - RF 88038 A35 - Eshiwani, Arthur A., 1988-1990 (Box 118, Folder 726A)
    - RF 88038 A42 - Olorunju, Phindile E., 1988-1990, 1992, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 727-728)
      African Dissertation Internship Award. Dissertation topic: "Groundnut Rosette: Disease Reaction and Inheritance of Resistance of Peanut Genotypes to Groundnut Rosette Virus and Groundnut Rosette Assistor Virus"
    - RF88038 A42 - Olorunju, Phindile E., 1988-1990, 1992, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 727A)
      Restricted - Confidentiall material
    - RF 88038 A48 - Munodawafa, Davison, 1987-1992, 1995. 1997 (Box 118, Folder 729)
      African Dissertation Internship Award. Dissertation topic: "The Use of Student Nurses on Community Assignment in the Implementation of Health Instruction in Rural Secondary Schools of Zimbabwe"
    - RF 88038 A48 - Munodawafa, Davison, 1987-1992, 1995, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 729A)